{"Title":"SonificationQuestionnaire","QuestionBlocks":[{"SubTitle":"Baseline","BlockQuestion":"","Questions":[{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","questionType":2,"likertIs5":false,"likertLowestText":"","likertHighestText":"","multiAnswers":["Yes","No"],"numberScaleMax":0,"numberScaleMin":0,"numPadDefaultValue":""},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","questionType":2,"likertIs5":false,"likertLowestText":"","likertHighestText":"","multiAnswers":["Yes","No"],"numberScaleMax":0,"numberScaleMin":0,"numPadDefaultValue":""},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sounds origins?","questionType":2,"likertIs5":false,"likertLowestText":"","likertHighestText":"","multiAnswers":["Yes","No"],"numberScaleMax":0,"numberScaleMin":0,"numPadDefaultValue":""}]},{"SubTitle":"Fases","BlockQuestion":"","Questions":[{"question":"Do you understand the condition 1 instruction?","questionType":2,"likertIs5":false,"likertLowestText":"","likertHighestText":"","multiAnswers":["Yes","No"],"numberScaleMax":0,"numberScaleMin":0,"numPadDefaultValue":""},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 1?","questionType":0,"likertIs5":false,"likertLowestText":"Not confident","likertHighestText":"Very confident","multiAnswers":["Yes","No"],"numberScaleMax":0,"numberScaleMin":0,"numPadDefaultValue":""},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 2 instruction?","questionType":2,"likertIs5":false,"likertLowestText":"","likertHighestText":"","multiAnswers":["Yes","No"],"numberScaleMax":0,"numberScaleMin":0,"numPadDefaultValue":""},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 2?","questionType":0,"likertIs5":false,"likertLowestText":"Not confident","likertHighestText":"Very confident","multiAnswers":["Yes","No"],"numberScaleMax":0,"numberScaleMin":0,"numPadDefaultValue":""},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 3 instruction?","questionType":2,"likertIs5":false,"likertLowestText":"","likertHighestText":"","multiAnswers":["Yes","No"],"numberScaleMax":0,"numberScaleMin":0,"numPadDefaultValue":""},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 3?","questionType":0,"likertIs5":false,"likertLowestText":"Not confident","likertHighestText":"Very confident","multiAnswers":["Yes","No"],"numberScaleMax":0,"numberScaleMin":0,"numPadDefaultValue":""},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 4 instruction?","questionType":2,"likertIs5":false,"likertLowestText":"","likertHighestText":"","multiAnswers":["Yes","No"],"numberScaleMax":0,"numberScaleMin":0,"numPadDefaultValue":""},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 4?","questionType":0,"likertIs5":false,"likertLowestText":"Not confident","likertHighestText":"Very confident","multiAnswers":["Yes","No"],"numberScaleMax":0,"numberScaleMin":0,"numPadDefaultValue":""},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 5 instruction?","questionType":2,"likertIs5":false,"likertLowestText":"","likertHighestText":"","multiAnswers":["Yes","No"],"numberScaleMax":0,"numberScaleMin":0,"numPadDefaultValue":""},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 5?","questionType":0,"likertIs5":false,"likertLowestText":"Not confident","likertHighestText":"Very confident","multiAnswers":["Yes","No"],"numberScaleMax":0,"numberScaleMin":0,"numPadDefaultValue":""}]}]}